Driven to learn quickly, advance computer proficiency and training in industry operations. Solid background in field and office settings supporting team needs. Flexible and hardworking team player focused on boosting productivity and performance with conscientious and detail-oriented approaches.

Hardworking Student offering part-time work experience and extensive knowledge of core subject matter. Meticulous and detail-oriented with excellent observational, organizational and communication skills.

Work History

2023-09

2023-07 - Student Intern

2023-09 No Previous Experience, New Delhi

2023-07 - Front End Developer

none, New Delhi

- Collaborated with stakeholders during development processes to confirm creative proposals and design best practices.
- Use regulatory and compliance standards for user interface designs.
- Advocated for well-tested and documented, high quality code.
- Guided customers on project stages and iterations with input on best practices, user needs and technology capabilities.

Education

2021-09 - Bachelor of Technology: Computer

Current Science

Chitkara University - Rajpura, Punjab

Certifications

2022-10 Cyber Security

2022-12 Digital Marketing

2023-04 UI/UX Desgining



Kaif Md
Web Developer

Contact

Address

Patna, India 800002

Phone

+919693848070

E-mail

kaifmd0407@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://in.linkedin.com/

Skills

Front End Development

Upper intermediate

Problem Solvina

Intermediate

Video Editing

Upper intermediate

Critical Thinking

Upper intermediate

Software

Web Development